I have to say leisurely.
I have to say I'm just I'm just trying
to think outside the box. I'm just, you
know,
intrusive thoughts, active mind, you
know, tinfoil hat. I started looking up
if they have a vaccination yet.
And it's funny because
Moderna, who
had the COVID vaccination really super
quickly, they have been meeting with a
college in Korea, which is where the
first outbreak happened of this
hand-foot virus back during the Korean
War. People from Moderna are over in
Korea
trying to develop a vaccination
to this virus.
And that research started in 2023.
So then I went down the rabbit hole and
I started thinking, you know, what's
been what's like Moderna been up to
lately? Last week, their stock went up
19%.
And just today, it's up another 4%. So
people are starting to invest. Who are
the shareholders of Moderna? Stéphane
Bancel is the CEO of Moderna. He grew up
in France. He lives in Boston where
Moderna headquarters is.
And he is worth $4.1 billion. He's a
year younger than me. Okay, that's
pretty humbling.
I'm just here building my portfolio. He
holds 8% of all of the entire shares of
Moderna. But Vanguard
Vanguard holds 42 million shares
of Moderna. That's about It equals about
10 to 12%
of all of the shares for that company.
The second investor,
surprise, surprise, is BlackRock. They
have 32.5
million shares in Moderna. If this
became something, like if this actually
became something, you know, 3 months
down the road, everything's closed,
we're in a massive pandemic. There could
be like a lot of people that
that financially benefit
if something like this happened again.
We're in trillions of dollars of debt in
this country.
I don't know. I'm just saying.
>> Hey.